[noisy crowd] Good afternoon.
[drums beating] Do come in. My name is Sir
cue-2
Commodity Taxom, and I have the honor to
be one of the two candidates standing for
cue-3
the new interest. Pick up a cockade, pin
it to your hat. Orange, that's our
cue-4
campaign color.
cue-5
Suits your complexion beautifully, if I
may say so. Take a seat. Have some
cue-6
champagne. Gin? Punch?
cue-7
What do we stand for? Liberty and loyalty.
You can see it on our flag. But just look
cue-8
at these people. They care more about how
much food and drink they can shovel down
cue-9
their throats. Wine, oysters, tobacco. Do
you have any idea how much this is
cue-10
costing me? It's illegal to bribe voters
with money, you see, so I must treat them
cue-11
with a banquet like this. [glass clinks]
Or with gifts for their wives and
cue-12
daughters. I owe that sour-looking man 20
pounds for all those gloves
cue-13
and stockings on the table. Believe me, I
loathe being here among these
cue-14
awful people. Oh, I apologize. Not you, of
course. But when there's an election, I
cue-15
need to show willing. If I want this man's
vote, I'm obliged to kiss his wife, even
cue-16
if he is setting fire to my wig. Have a
care, sir.
cue-17
Will it be worth it? Well, if I get
elected into Parliament, that's influence
cue-18
and money for me. And yes, if enough of us
whigs win, we'll be able to keep those
cue-19
Tories out of government. But Lord, the
indignity. And this
cue-20
is only the start of the campaign.